It allows for passive and constant mobility of the interperitoneal fluid,
它允许腹膜间液的被动和持续流动，
intraperitoneal.
腹膜内。
It participates in your gait if you have a peritoneal fixation.
如果您有腹膜固定，它会影响您的步态。
The upper limbs, the lower limbs are also an
上肢、下肢也是您腹膜囊的
expansion of your peritoneal sac.
延伸。
What happens here can be the expression of a development here.
这里发生的事情可能是这里发展的一种表达。
It is a cellular, tissue, molecular continuity.
这是一种细胞、组织、分子，
and even energetic.
甚至是能量的连续性。
The peritoneum can fixate.
腹膜可能会固定。
You must consider the peritoneum as an active and current organ,
您必须将腹膜视为一个活跃且当前的器官，
meaning it has immune protective capabilities.
也就是说，它具有免疫保护能力。
This leads us to have to consider the peritoneum as an organ.
这使我们必须将腹膜视为一个器官。
The peritoneum releases tissue hormones, prostaglandins,
腹膜会根据分泌和吸收释放组织激素，即前列腺素。
depending on secretion and absorption.
根据分泌和吸收。
This means that it will try to maintain a more or less constant fluid volume,
这意味着它将尝试保持或多或少恒定的液体体积，
which is quite close.
这与脑脊液非常接近。
of cerebrospinal fluid. At the moment I have the integration of my external coelom
当我将我的外体腔整合到内体腔时，
into
这与我的神经管整合在相同的发展动力学中。
the integration
整合
of my neural tube. It's as if I integrate the amniotic fluid into my
我的神经管。就好像我将羊水整合到我的神经管中，
neural tube and
我的神经管和
I integrate the extra-coelomic fluid into my peritoneal system.
我将胚外体腔液整合到我的腹膜系统中。
This ends on the 28th day,
这在第28天结束，
it happens at the same time.
这是同时发生的。
I have a kind of peritoneal volume that always tries to keep a
我有一个腹膜体积，它总是试图保持一个常数，
constant
常数
to have a homeostatic hydrostatic volume,
以获得稳态类型的静水体积，
both cerebrally and peritoneally.
无论是在大脑层面还是在腹膜层面。
There is a transmembrane tension that contains interstitial components
存在跨膜张力，其中包含所有邻近器官的间质成分，
of all neighboring organs,
所有邻近器官的间质成分，
which is informed about the digestive state, about the metabolic state
它被告知所有周围器官的消化状态和代谢状态。
of all surrounding organs.
所有周围器官。
in its interstitial fluid.
在其间质液中。
There is no inside.
没有内部。
It's an exchange together.
这是一个整体的交换。
There are molecular exchanges.
存在分子交换。
I have mesenchymal cells
我有间充质细胞
that were beyond the precordial plate
它们位于脊索前板之外
which will become the pericardium and the septum transversum
它们将成为心包和横膈膜。
which are integrated by the global movement of my embryo.
它们通过我胚胎的整体运动而整合。
And at the moment I have this development of the heart
当我心脏发育的时候
that is setting up, which is a fulcrum,
它开始形成，这是一个支撑点，
there is a meeting of the heart on the upper part of my vesicle.
心脏与我囊泡的上部相遇。
And this meeting will integrate these mesenchymal cells that can express themselves
这次相遇将整合这些间充质细胞，它们可以表达
and form the primitive septum transversum.
并形成原始横膈膜。
And this primitive septum transversum integrates between the 22nd day and closes,
这个原始横膈膜在第22天到第28天之间整合并
we could say, in a delimited way around the 28th day.
可以说，在第28天左右完成。
The peritoneum is an organ in which there are arterioles that have an osmotic exchange
腹膜是一个器官，其中有小动脉，它们与血浆进行渗透性交换。
with blood plasma.
与血浆进行渗透性交换。
So there are kinds of exudates that inform it.
所以有一些渗出物可以提供信息。
on the intracellular vegetative state,
关于细胞内植物状态，
that it is all the time and completely,
它始终完全地，
by this plasma exchange, informed.
通过这种血浆交换，得到信息。
There are mesothelial cells like macrophages,
有间皮细胞，如巨噬细胞，
like polymorphonuclear cells, like mast cells,
如多形核细胞，如肥大细胞，
which will determine defense reactions at the peritoneal level.
它们将决定腹膜水平的防御反应。
Mast cells are sensitive to immunoglobulins E, to IgE.
肥大细胞对免疫球蛋白E，即IgE敏感。
So everything that is allergy, asthma, etc.,
所以所有过敏、哮喘等，
are the same mast cells that are present at the level of the article.
都是在支气管水平存在的相同肥大细胞，当你受到感染因子攻击时，
bronchial that when you have an aggression of an infectious agent at the level of the
支气管水平存在的相同肥大细胞，当你受到感染因子攻击时，
peritoneum, it can cause mast cell degranulation on another
腹膜，这可能导致肥大细胞脱颗粒，在另一个
level. I'm allergic to milk, I have a poor immune barrier at the level of
层面。我对牛奶过敏，我的膜免疫屏障不好。
my membrane. Macromolecules that should not pass, pass. There is a
不应该通过的大分子通过了。有一个
mast cell reaction. What do I do? An asthmatic reaction, bronchitis
肥大细胞反应。我该怎么办？哮喘反应，支气管炎
in an external space while the infectious agent is initially
在一个外部空间，而感染因子最初是在
peritoneal.
腹膜。
Because I have this same balance in terms of IgE.
因为我在IGE方面有相同的平衡。
But I'm going to have a distant reaction.
但我会做出一个远距离的反应。
I have eczema in a child.
我让一个孩子得了湿疹。
Good job, my friend, you found a correct way out.
干得好，伙计，你找到了一个正确的出口。
We're going to try to remove the allergen.
我们将尝试去除过敏原。
But there, you found a way out.
但是，你已经找到了一个出口。
We're going to give you cortisone.
我们会给你可的松。
I'm bringing it in.
我让它进来。
The skin is also an expression of your cerebrospinal fluid,
皮肤也是你脑脊液的一种表达，
in its earliest expression on the autogenetic level.
在其自生发生学上最早的表达中。
But it is also an expression of your tube.
但它也是你消化道的一种表达。
digestive. The digestive tract is an external tissue. And so, what I'm trying to make
消化道。消化道是一种外部组织。所以，我试图
come out here, if it's blocked, I'll express it here.
在这里排出的东西，如果被阻塞，我就会在这里表达出来。
And at the level of the digestive tract, how
Et  au  niveau  du  tube  digestif,  comment
do I express it? I express it either by asthma, because I will
j 'exprime  ?  J 'exprime  soit  par  un  asthme,  parce  que  je  vais
demacify it, or by
le  démacier,  ou  bien  par
bronchitis. I'm going to produce mucus, an exudate. I'm going to get it
une  bronchite.  Je  vais  sortir  du  mucus,  d 'une  production  d 'exudate.  Je  le  fais
out as
sortir  comme
best I can. I'm going to give you bronchodilators now.
je peux. Je vais te donner maintenant des bronchodilatateurs.
I'm going to give antibiotics but I haven't solved the problem, it was perhaps simply
je vais donner des antibiotiques mais j'ai pas résolu le problème c'était peut-être simplement
an allergen like a strawberry
un agent allergène de type une fraise